[{"answer": "Are we going out", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pilot-Part-2.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Do you want me to break up with you", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "I don't even know what you're talking about", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pilot-Part-2.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "All right. We're broken up", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Ah! You're fine. There's nothing wrong with you. I'm the one who's dying", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pilot-Part-2.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Because I can't act! I stink! I don't what I'm doing", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "What about me? I was a total failure. Everything was fine. Now this thing's gonna be a success and God's gonna give me a terminal disease", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pilot-Part-2.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "The guy playing my friend threatened me", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "my friend, are you in wardrobe? my friend", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pilot-Part-2.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "my friend", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Hello, my friend", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pilot-Part-2.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Why don't you start in the bedroom", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Hello. So, where do you want me to start today", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pilot-Part-2.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": " Start in the bedroom...", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Hey. The butler's here", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pilot-Part-2.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "I'm not sending him to your house", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Well, it goes fast.", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pilot-Part-2.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Hello.", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "What's all this about", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pilot-Part-2.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "You had a date? You went out with my butler? Who said you could go out with my butler", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": " Hello", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pilot-Part-2.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Oh, hi my friend", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "I didn't know that he'd fall for me and I'd drive him insane. I mean, you know, that's not my fault", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pilot-Part-2.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "I can't believe this? What happened to him? Where the hell is he", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "my friend, my friend, lunch and dinner? Boy, you guys ought to move in. How about a piece of pie on me? my friend! Take care of these fellows", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pilot-Part-2.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Get away with what", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "You must be very proud Mr. my friend.  And may I say sir they're lovely girls, absolutely lovely girls. It's nice to see such fine upstanding women in gainful employment, Mr. my friend", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pilot-Part-2.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "A table right here", "qsentId": 28}]